[Music] I
[Música]
also wanted to comment on something that
también quería comentar una cosa que me
has made me very Well, it has obviously made me very
ha hecho mucha Bueno me ha dado mucha
happy because it is very good news okay, it is very good news what is happening well, they sent me this afternoon a video that was uploaded to YouTube a few months ago
subió en YouTube hace unos meses en
specifically
concreto
uh specifically 5 months
eh en concreto 5 meses
no 5 months I think 50 months not the
no 5 meses creo s 5co meses no la La
farewell of Escaleto they said not an
despedida de escaleto decían no en
exclusive no exclusive huge
exclusiva no exclusiva gordísima
exclusive we have an exclusive
exclusiva tenemos una exclusiva Bueno
Well that exclusive uh it is going to stay
pues esa exclusiva eh se se va a quedar
in the drawer for the moment like the like
en el cajón de momento como la como la
Vita Dynamita's lawsuit against Marta Riesco
demanda de Vita dinamita a Marta riesco
no and the thing is that luckily luckily that
no y es que por suerte por suerte esa
exclusive about Escaleto's dismissal well it was not it was not
exclusiva del despido de escaleto pues
true Escaleto has returned
no era no era verdad escaleto ha vuelto
I sincerely have to tell you that I
yo sinceramente tengo que deciros que
knew something okay I knew something I don't remember
sabía algo vale sabía algo no me acuerdo
exactly where I found out María a
exactamente por dónde lo supe María un
kiss a kiss María how strong she was
beso un beso María qué fuerte que tenía
right How strong what happened today eh How strong
razón Qué fuerte lo de hoy eh Qué fuerte
what happened today eh I don't mean to pat myself on the back
lo de hoy eh No es por echarme flores
but the thing about Escaleto reached me I don't know
pero yo lo de escaleto me llegó no sé en
specifically why Because you know that I
concreto Por qué Porque ya sabéis que
talk to a lot of people  all
hablo con mucha gente al cabo de todo el
day is also worth it It is true that
día vale también Es verdad que han
several collaborators from Sálvame have been through here
pasado por aquí varios colaboradores de
as if we were
de sálvame de ni que fuéramos han pasado
several have passed by, at least four
varios no han pasado por lo menos cuatro
or five have passed by I don't know the truth I don't know
o cinco No lo sé la verdad no lo sé con
who we spoke with but I mean it's something
quién lo hablamos pero o sea es una cosa
that eh small committee and between colleagues it was
que eh pettit comité y entre compañeros
known I didn't know exactly exactly
se sabía no sabía exactamente
what it was not what
exactamente de qué era no lo que le
had happened to the boy but it had
había pasado al muchacho pero sí que me
come to me that he was unwell
había llegado como que estaba malillo
Okay then they haven't fired him I don't know why they
Vale entonces no lo han despedido no sé
make that up Seriously not
por qué se inventan eso De verdad no
everything is worth it let's see a little about
todo vale a ver vamos a ver un poco la
the reinstatement of Escaleto And what
la reincorporación de escaleto Y qué es
has happened to him with all of you
lo que le ha pasado con todos ustedes
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Escaleto Okay well well how strong
escaleto Bueno bueno bueno que fuerte
listen to me I didn't know you were coming today eh
escúchame que no sabía que venías hoy eh
Neither you nor anyone Well I did you did
Ni tú ni nadie Bueno yo sí tú sí lo
know I knew And since when did I know
sabías Yo lo sabía Y desde cuándo lo sab
Look here
pues Mirad aquí
here Escaleto tells you what was
aquí os dice escaleto qué es lo que le
wrong with him Okay what happened to him and
pasaba Vale qué es lo que le ha pasado y
why he has been on leave Look it hasn't
por qué ha estado de baja Mira no ha
happened I haven't had a child through
pasado no he tenido un hijo por
surrogacy Javi hasn't been to me
gestación subrogada no me ha eestado
holes in a basement I wish with a
Javi de hoyos en un sótano Ojalá con una
cross there a harness and everything I would have
cruz ahí un arnés y de todo me hubiera
loved but it hasn't been like that Javi I'll
encantado pero no ha sido así Javi te
give you ideas
doy ideas
eh They haven't kicked me out no I don't know I don't
eh No me han echado no no sé no me
remember they've told me more things But
acuerdo me han contado más cosas Pero
well none of that has happened what has
bueno nada de eso ha pasado lo que ha
happened has been something much simpler
pasado ha sido algo mucho más simple
much more plain eh something that happens to a
mucho más llano eh algo que le pasa a
lot of people Eh that has six letters that is
mucha gente Eh que tiene seis letras que
eh
es eh
cancer Look it hasn't happened poor thing What a
cáncer Mira no ha pasado pobrecillo Qué
scare eh poor thing eh look there
susto eh pobrecillo eh mira ahí se
Belén hugs herself with escaleto for this chair
abraza Belén con escaleto por es sillo
eh I think it was the testicles no
eh creo que era de los testículos no
because I saw how later on let's see
porque he visto como más adelante a ver
these
estos
gold I think it was the testicles
oro creo que era de los testículos
because I saw like a t that said something about
porque he visto como un t que decía algo
always touching I don't know a And it was like
de tocaro siempre no sé a Y fue así
literally yes Belén I'm very angry
literal sí Belén estoy muy enfadada
with you and I say to her Why why haven't you
contigo y le digo Por qué por qué no me
told me that you're bad with what I
has contado que estás malo con lo que yo
love you Who is
quiero Quién es
or Hey let's team up I'm busy
o Oye que teamos loo que estoy ocupado
who
quién
are you what you haven't told me I say
eres qué no me lo has dicho le digo
Belén Well why were you going to get like that and I didn't
Belén Pues por te ibas a poner así y no
want you to get  so but why did
quería que te pusieras así pero por qué
n't you tell me with how much I
no me lo has dicho con lo que yo te
love you that I and also since Belén is very much like
quiero que yo y además pues como es muy
all my heart and such that I make your
Belén todo corazón y tal que yo te hago
food that I take you to the doctor they
la comida que te llevo al médico te han
took you to the doctor I say let's see Belén
llevado al médico digo a ver Belén que
my family is here my friends are here I've been
está mi familia están mis amigos he
mega supported Of course my mother
estado mega arropado Claro mi madre se
came here my father too my sister eh
vino aquí mi padre también mi hermana eh
And I tell her yes yes that I'm fine and I
Y le digo que sí que sí que estoy bien y
say it's Vera that I didn't tell you And it was like
digo es Vera que no te lo dije Y fue así
literally the belaa eh all helpful Look
literal la belaa eh todo servicial Mira
yes This was the tck that maybe I saw not
sí Este era el tck que a lo mejor vi no
touched the balls By the way guys that
tocados los huevos Por cierto chicos que
you see me kids that you have
me veis chiques que tenéis genitales
male genitals I don't care Ah touched it is a
masculinos me da igual Ah tocado es
lot the balls because it is true that you
mucho los huevos porque es verdad que
can see this very soon it is also
esto lo puedes ver muy pronto es además
something that in the case of the testicles of
algo que en el caso de los testículos de
boys it is easy to see it is not
los chicos es fácil de ver no es a lo
maybe like a breast or like a cancer that
mejor como una mama o como un cáncer que
is inside the body that is very
esté dentro del cuerpo que es muy
complicated and that maybe It gives signs
complicado y que a lo mejor Da señales
when it is too late but the
cuando es muy tarde pero que cuanto
sooner you look at it the better I always p
antes os lo miréis mejor yo siempre me p
Jo Well yes if I had gone to the
Jo Pues si si hubiera ido antes al
doctor earlier or I had done it earlier  the
médico o me hubiera hecho antes la
ultrasound, well it would have gone better for me, maybe I would have
ecografía pues mejor me hubiera ido a lo
even had to give a repel, no, repel, no, well, he
incluso qu repel no que repeli no bueno
says that I suppose it will be like that, he doesn't say that yes, that if
dice Que supongo que será así no dice
you take it in time and
que si que si te lo coges a tiempo y
so on, that that forward, Sid, very
demás que que que para adelante Sid muy
quickly, also, no, because this boy, I
rápido además no porque este muchacho o
mean, it hasn't been that long since he was there, no, I mean,
sea no hace tanto que estuvo ahí no o
how long has he been on sick leave, he's been there for
sea cuánto tiempo ha estado de baja ha
4 months, five Maybe, if anything, I do
estado 4 meses cinco A lo mejor si acaso
n't know, kidnap
no sé
me and make me yours, I'll tell you Javi.
secuéstrame y hazme tuyo escaleto a Javi
Well, I'm glad the boy is there, let's face it, I really
Bueno pues me alegro que esté ahí el
like him,
son me simpatiza mucho la verdad
boy. So, great, I saw him, eh, I
muchacho Así que genial yo lo vi eh yo
saw him in person, I'll tell you when I went
lo vi en persona escaleto cuando fui a
to the Chinese story, he
lo de cuando fui a lo de cuento chino
was there, I saw him in the
estaba al escaleto allí lo vi en la
office, I saw him in the office. How are you,
oficina lo vi en la oficina Qué tal
Victor? How are you all who are
Víctor qué tal a todos los que vais
coming in? Well, I'm glad you're all
entrando Bueno pues me alegro que estéis
joining the live show because today
incorporándose al directo porque hoy
we have a lot of fun, 7 months, it's been almost
tenemos mucho moño 7 meses ha sido casi
eight, my goodness. Well, but it's fast. No,
ocho madre mía Bueno pero es rápido No
I wish, I wish all things were, 7
ojalá ojalá todas las cosas fueran 7
months, no, I wish all things were,  It has
meses no ojalá todas las cosas fueran
n't been fast, so I
así no ha sido rápido no así que
understand that if you catch it in time, it
entiendo que si lo pillas a a tiempo
's a curious thing
pues es una una cosa curiosa
[Music]
[Música]